A Guide to the Asian Cultural Council records, Administrative Files, RG 1 FA427
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Administrative, 1952, 1954-2006; 1; 108.25 Cubic Feet 246 document boxes.
  - ACC records, 1955-1958, 1960-2006; 2
    - Director's Office, 1955-1958, 1960-1998; 5
      - International Agencies, 1966, 1968-1989, 1992; 6
        - International Council of Museums (ICOM-CIMAM), Correspondence, 1966, 1971-1975, 1977, 1979, 1983 (Box 182, Folder 4253)
        - International Council of Museums (ICOM-CIMAM), Correspondence with Luis Monreal (Folder 1 of 2), 1966, 1968-1974, 1977-1979, 1981-1982, 1984-1989 (Box 182, Folder 4254)
        - International Council of Museums (ICOM-CIMAM), Correspondence with Luis Monreal (Folder 2 of 2), 1966, 1968-1974, 1977-1979, 1981-1982, 1984-1989 (Box 182, Folder 4255)
        - International Council of Museums (ICOM-CIMAM), Illicit Art Export Articles, 1968-1975, 1983 (Box 182, Folder 4256)
        - International Council of Museums (ICOM-CIMAM), Membership, 1983 (Box 182, Folder 4257)
        - International Council of Museums (ICOM-CIMAM), Other Committees, 1969, 1971-1973, 1976, 1981, 1984 (Box 182, Folder 4258)
        - International Council of Museums (ICOM-CIMAM), Regional Agency in Asia, 1972, 1974, 1976, 1980, 1983-1984 (Box 182, Folder 4259)
        - International Council on Monuments & Sites (ICOMOS/US-ICOMOS), General Correspondence, 1965, 1969, 1986-1988 (Box 182, Folder 4260)
        - International Council on Monuments & Sites (ICOMOS/US-ICOMOS), Correspondence with Terry Morton, 1984-1986 (Box 182, Folder 4261)
        - International Institute for Comparative Music Studies and Documentation, 1967-1968, 1970, 1974-1975, 1988 (Box 183, Folder 4262)
        - International Music Council, 1963-1964, 1966-1969, 1972-1973, 1981 (Box 183, Folder 4263)
        - United Nations Educational, Scientific and Cultural Organization (UNESCO), 1974, 1976-1979, 1981-1982, 1988 (Box 183, Folder 4264)
        - United Nations Educational, Scientific and Cultural Organization (UNESCO), General Correspondence, 1976-1988 (Box 183, Folder 4265)
      - Other Organizations, 1968, 1980, 1985-1992; 7
        - Belgium, Canada, Egypt, Spain, General, 1980, 1985-1989 (Box 183, Folder 4266)
        - England & France, General, 1968, 1980, 1990-1992 (Box 183, Folder 4267)
        - Switzerland, Tribal Art Centre, 1985-1988 (Box 183, Folder 4268)
      - U. S. Educational Institutions, 1963-1991; 8
        - A-B, 1970, 1982-1987 (Box 184, Folder 4269)
        - Brown University, 1983-1985, 1987 (Box 184, Folder 4270)
        - C, 1968, 1970-1971, 1973, 1975-1977, 1981, 1983-1990 (Box 184, Folder 4271)
        - C, 1968, 1970-1971, 1973, 1975-1977, 1981, 1983-1990 (Box 184, Folder 4271A)
        - California, University of, Berkeley, 1967-1970, 1972-1978, 1980, 1982-1984, 1986-1988 (Box 184, Folder 4272)
        - California, University of, Los Angeles, 1963-1964, 1967-1975, 1978-1979, 1981, 1990-1991 (Box 184, Folder 4273)
        - Colorado, University of, 1969, 1972-1973, 1977-1978, 1980, 1982 (Box 184, Folder 4274)
        - Columbia University (Folder 1 of 3), 1963-1965, 1967-1970, 1973-1988 (Box 185, Folder 4275)
        - Columbia University (Folder 2 of 3), 1963-1965, 1967-1970, 1973-1988 (Box 185, Folder 4276)
        - Columbia University (Folder 3 of 3), 1963-1965, 1967-1970, 1973-1988 (Box 185, Folder 4277)
        - Cornell University, 1968-1969, 1972, 1975-1976, 1978-1984, 1986, 1988-1991 (Box 185, Folder 4278)
        - D-F, 1964-1966, 1968-1970, 1972-1974, 1976-1977, 1979, 1981-1983, 1987-1990 (Box 185, Folder 4279)
        - Davis & Elkins College, 1981-1984 (Box 185, Folder 4280)
        - Iowa, University of, 1971, 1979-1983, 1987-1988 (Box 186, Folder 4281)
        - Kala Institute, 1978, 1980-1981 (Box 186, Folder 4282)
        - M-N, 1968, 1974-1975, 1978-1979, 1981-1987 (Box 186, Folder 4283)
        - Maryland, University of, College Park, 1971, 1974-1977, 1979-1983, 1985-1988 (Box 186, Folder 4284)
        - Northeastern Illinois University, 1977-1978 (Box 186, Folder 4285)
        - O-S, 1970-1972, 1978-1981, 1985-1989 (Box 186, Folder 4286)
        - Wisconsin, University of, 1978, 1980-1982, 1986-1987, 1990 (Box 186, Folder 4287)
      - U. S. Foundations, 1964-1991; 9
        - A, 1981-1983, 1987 (Box 186, Folder 4288)
        - The Buddhayana Foundation, Inc., 1974-1975, 1983-1984 (Box 186, Folder 4289)
        - China Institute of America, 1969-1970, 1974-1977, 1980-1981, 1986-1990 (Box 187, Folder 4290)
        - Chinese Culture Foundation of San Francisco, Correspondence, 1969-1970, 1972, 1977, 1979, 1981, 1983-1984 (Box 187, Folder 4291)
        - Dance Perspectives Foundation, 1975, 1982, 1987-1988, 1990 (Box 187, Folder 4292)
        - E, 1982-1984 (Box 187, Folder 4293)
        - F, 1973, 1978-1989, 1983-1987, 1990 (Box 187, Folder 4294)
        - Film News Foundation, 1985-1987, 1989-1990 (Box 187, Folder 4295)
        - Ford Foundation, Asia, Correspondence (Folder 1 of 2), 1968-1986, 1990 (Box 187, Folder 4296)
        - Ford Foundation, Asia, Correspondence (Folder 2 of 2), 1968-1986, 1990 (Box 188, Folder 4297)
        - Ford Foundation, Asia Miscellaneous, Correspondence with Adrienne Germain, 1982-1984 (Box 188, Folder 4298)
        - Ford Foundation, Asia Miscellaneous, Report on Art in Thailand, 1978, 1980 (Box 188, Folder 4299)
        - Ford Foundation, Asia Miscellaneous, Richard S. Lanier Trip to Asia for Ford Foundation, 1980 (Box 188, Folder 4300)
        - Ford Foundation, Asia Miscellaneous, Richard S. Lanier Trip to Asia for Ford Foundation, 1980 (Box 188, Folder 4300A)
        - Ford Foundation, Indonesia, Correspondence with Tom Kessinger, & David Winder, 1981-1987, 1991 (Box 188, Folder 4301)
        - Ford Foundation, New York Office, Correspondence, 1964-1965, 1967-1968, 1971-1985 (Box 188, Folder 4302)
        - Ford Foundation, New York Office, Correspondence with David Finkelstein, 1976 (Box 188, Folder 4303)
        - Ford Foundation, New York Office, Correspondence with Sidney Jones, 1983-1984 (Box 188, Folder 4304)
        - Ford Foundation, New York Office, Fundraising Proposal to Match National Endowment of the Humanities, 1986 (Box 188, Folder 4305)
        - Ford Foundation, New York Office, Notes on Meeting with Indira Gandhi, 1981-1982 (Box 188, Folder 4306)
        - Ford Foundation, New York Office, Richard S. Lanier's Remarks at Ford, 1983 (Box 188, Folder 4307)
        - Foundation Center, 1966, 1969-1971, 1973, 1978-1982, 1991 (Box 188, Folder 4308)
        - H, 1970, 1975-1976, 1981, 1984, 1986-1988 (Box 189, Folder 4309)
        - I, 1972, 1978-1987, 1990-1991 (Box 189, Folder 4310)
        - J-M, 1970, 1979-1982, 1984, 1986, 1988, 1996 (Box 189, Folder 4311)
        - Samuel H. Kress Foundation, 1981-1982, 1984-1987 (Box 189, Folder 4312)
        - N, 1976-1977, 1980-1984, 1986-1987, 1989-1991 (Box 189, Folder 4313)
        - P-Q, 1968, 1970, 1982-1984, 1986, 1990 (Box 189, Folder 4314)
        - R, 1968, 1973, 1981-1982, 1984, 1987-1990 (Box 189, Folder 4315)
        - S, 1987-1990 (Box 189, Folder 4316)
        - Starr Foundation, 1968, 1972-1973, 1981-1989, 1991, 1993 (Box 190, Folder 4317)
        - T-W, 1969, 1978-1979, 1982, 1984, 1986, 1989 (Box 190, Folder 4318)
        - Twyla Tharp Dance Foundation, 1981-1985 (Box 190, Folder 4319)
      - U. S. Individuals, 1960-1961, 1963-1997; 10
        - A, 1965, 1970-1994
          - Ab-Ag, 1980-1990, 1992-1994 (Box 190, Folder 4320)
          - Ab-Ag, 1980-1990, 1992-1994 (Box 190, Folder 4320A)
          - Ak-All, 1982-1985, 1989-1994 (Box 190, Folder 4321)
          - Ak-All, 1982-1985, 1989-1994 (Box 190, Folder 4321A)
          - Als-An, 1965, 1970-1972, 1974-1977, 1980-1983, 1985-1986, 1989-1994 (Box 190, Folder 4322)
          - Ao-Armi, 1974, 1980-1981, 1984-1988, 1990-1991, 1994 (Box 191, Folder 4323)
          - Ao-Armi, 1974, 1980-1981, 1984-1988, 1990-1991, 1994 (Box 191, Folder 4323A)
          - Arms-Au, 1973, 1978, 1980-1981, 1983-1989, 1992-1994 (Box 191, Folder 4324)
          - Arms-Au, 1973, 1978, 1980-1981, 1983-1989, 1992-1994 (Box 191, Folder 4324A)
          - Av-Az, 1972-1974, 1976-1977, 1979-1987 ,1989, 1992 (Box 191, Folder 4325)
        - B, 1968-1969, 1973-1994, 1997
          - Bab-Ban, 1969, 1974-1983, 1987-1993 (Box 191, Folder 4326)
          - Bab-Ban, 1969, 1974-1983, 1987-1993 (Box 191, Folder 4326A)
            Restricted pfrom scholarly access-Confidential materials
          - Bara-Barn, 1981-1984, 1986-1994 (Box 191, Folder 4327)
          - Bara-Barn, 1981-1984, 1986-1994 (Box 191, Folder 4327A)
          - Baro-Barr, 1973-1975, 1977, 1979-1980, 1982-1986, 1988, 1990-1991, 1993 (Box 192, Folder 4328)
          - Baro-Barr, 1973-1975, 1977, 1979-1980, 1982-1986, 1988, 1990-1991, 1993 (Box 192, Folder 4328A)
          - Bart-Bas, 1968-1969, 1981-1987, 1989-1994 (Box 192, Folder 4329)
          - Bart-Bas, 1968-1969, 1981-1987, 1989-1994 (Box 192, Folder 4329A)
          - Bat-Bec, 1980-1983, 1985-1994 (Box 192, Folder 4330)
          - Bat-Bec, 1980-1983, 1985-1994 (Box 192, Folder 4330A)
          - Bee-Bek, 1974, 1981, 1986, 1988-1993 (Box 192, Folder 4331)
          - Bee-Bek, 1974, 1981, 1986, 1988-1993 (Box 192, Folder 4331A)
          - Bel-Ben, 1981-1987, 1990, 1992-1993 (Box 192, Folder 4332)
          - Bel-Ben, 1981-1987, 1990, 1992-1993 (Box 192, Folder 4332A)
          - Ber, 1968-1970, 1972, 1975-1976, 1980, 1982, 1984-1987, 1989-1992 (Box 193, Folder 4333)
          - Ber, 1968-1970, 1972, 1975-1976, 1980, 1982, 1984-1987, 1989-1992 (Box 193, Folder 4333A)
          - Bet-Blai, 1979-1983, 1985-1987, 1989-1993, 1997 (Box 193, Folder 4334)
          - Bet-Blai, 1979-1983, 1985-1987, 1989-1993, 1997 (Box 193, Folder 4334A)
            Restricted from scholarly access-Confidentail material
          - Blak-Blo, 1982, 1986-1991 (Box 193, Folder 4335)
          - Blak-Blo, 1982, 1986-1991 (Box 193, Folder 4335A)
          - Blum-Bo, 1981-1990, 1992 (Box 193, Folder 4336)
          - Blum-Bo, 1981-1990, 1992 (Box 193, Folder 4336A)
          - Bognar, Botond, 1988, 1992-1993 (Box 193, Folder 4337)
          - Bognar, Botond, 1988, 1992-1993 (Box 193, Folder 4337A)
          - Bra, 1976, 1981-1985, 1987, 1989-1990 (Box 194, Folder 4338)
          - Bra, 1976, 1981-1985, 1987, 1989-1990 (Box 194, Folder 4338A)
          - Brandon, James, 1968-1978 (Box 194, Folder 4339)
          - Bre-Bro, 1981-1982, 1984, 1986-1990, 1992 (Box 194, Folder 4340)
          - Bre-Bro, 1981-1982, 1984, 1986-1990, 1992 (Box 194, Folder 4340A)
          - Brn-Bul, 1979, 1981, 1984-1994 (Box 194, Folder 4341)
          - Brn-Bul, 1979, 1981, 1984-1994 (Box 194, Folder 4341A)
          - Bun-Bux, 1973-1976, 1978, 1980-1983, 1985-1994 (Box 194, Folder 4342)
          - Bun-Bux, 1973-1976, 1978, 1980-1983, 1985-1994 (Box 194, Folder 4342A)
        - C, 1970, 1973, 1976-1994, 1997
          - Cah-Carn, 1970, 1983-1989, 1992-1994 (Box 195, Folder 4343)
          - Cah-Carn, 1970, 1983-1989, 1992-1994 (Box 195, Folder 4343A)
          - Caro-Cav, 1978-1989, 1991 (Box 195, Folder 4344)
          - Caro-Cav, 1978-1989, 1991 (Box 195, Folder 4344A)
          - Cha, 1973, 1980-1981, 1983, 1985, 1987-1990, 1992-1994 (Box 195, Folder 4345)
          - Cha, 1973, 1980-1981, 1983, 1985, 1987-1990, 1992-1994 (Box 195, Folder 4345A)
            Restricted from s cholarly access-Confidential material
          - Che-Chop, 1980, 1983, 1985-1988, 1990-1994 (Box 195, Folder 4346)
          - Che-Chop, 1980, 1983, 1985-1988, 1990-1994 (Box 195, Folder 4346A)
          - Childs-Johnson, Elizabeth, 1988-1991 (Box 195, Folder 4347)
          - Chow-Cl, 1976-1978, 1981-1985, 1987-1990, 1992-1993, 1997 (Box 195, Folder 4348)
          - Chow-Cl, 1976-1978, 1981-1985, 1987-1990, 1992-1993, 1997 (Box 195, Folder 4348A)
          - Coa-Com, 1982, 1984-1994 (Box 196, Folder 4349)
          - Coa-Com, 1982, 1984-1994 (Box 196, Folder 4349A)
            Restricted from scholalry access-Confidential material
          - Con-Coo, 1983-1984, 1986-1994 (Box 196, Folder 4350)
          - Con-Coo, 1983-1984, 1986-1994 (Box 196, Folder 4350A)
          - Cop-Cri, 1981-1994 (Box 196, Folder 4351)
          - Cop-Cri, 1981-1994 (Box 196, Folder 4351A)
          - Cro-Cy, 1982-1994 (Box 196, Folder 4352)
          - Cro-Cy, 1982-1994 (Box 196, Folder 4352A)
            Restricfted from scholarly access-Confidential material
        - D, 1977-1994
          - Dag-Dau, 1979-1982, 1984, 1986-1994 (Box 196, Folder 4353)
          - Dag-Dau, 1979-1982, 1984, 1986-1994 (Box 196, Folder 4353A)
          - Dav-Del, 1980-1981, 1983-1986, 1988-1994 (Box 197, Folder 4354)
          - Dav-Del, 1980-1981, 1983-1986, 1988-1994 (Box 197, Folder 4354A)
          - Dem-Dig, 1981-1982, 1984-1986, 1990-1994 (Box 197, Folder 4355)
          - Dem-Dig, 1981-1982, 1984-1986, 1990-1994 (Box 197, Folder 4355A)
          - Dil-Don, 1978-1981, 1983-1984, 1987-1988, 1991, 1993-1994 (Box 197, Folder 4356)
          - Dil-Don, 1978-1981, 1983-1984, 1987-1988, 1991, 1993-1994 (Box 197, Folder 4356A)
          - Dor-Dug, 1977-1978, 1980, 1982, 1985-1994 (Box 197, Folder 4357)
          - Dor-Dug, 1977-1978, 1980, 1982, 1985-1994 (Box 197, Folder 4357A)
          - Dun-Dy, 1981, 1985, 1988-1989, 1991-1993 (Box 197, Folder 4358)
          - Dun-Dy, 1981, 1985, 1988-1989, 1991-1993 (Box 197, Folder 4358A)
        - E, 1975-1976, 1978-1982, 1984-1994
          - Ea-Em, 1975-1976, 1978-1979, 1981-1982, 1984-1988, 1990, 1992-1993 (Box 198, Folder 4359)
          - Ea-Em, 1975-1976, 1978-1979, 1981-1982, 1984-1988, 1990, 1992-1993 (Box 198, Folder 4359A)
          - En-Ey, 1980-1982, 1984, 1987-1994 (Box 198, Folder 4360)
          - En-Ey, 1980-1982, 1984, 1987-1994 (Box 198, Folder 4360A)
        - F, 1978-1994, 1996
          - Fa-Fer, 1980-1991, 1994 (Box 198, Folder 4361)
          - Fa-Fer, 1980-1991, 1994 (Box 198, Folder 4361A)
          - Fes-Fis, 1980, 1983-1992, 1996 (Box 198, Folder 4362)
          - Fes-Fis, 1980, 1983-1992, 1996 (Box 198, Folder 4362A)
          - Fit-Fo, 1981-1982, 1984-1986, 1988-1994, 1996 (Box 198, Folder 4363)
          - Fit-Fo, 1981-1982, 1984-1986, 1988-1994, 1996 (Box 198, Folder 4363A)
          - Fra, 1980, 1984-1990, 1992-1993 (Box 199, Folder 4364)
          - Fra, 1980, 1984-1990, 1992-1993 (Box 199, Folder 4364A)
          - Fraleigh, Sondra, 1988-1989 (Box 199, Folder 4365)
          - Fraleigh, Sondra, 1988-1989 (Box 199, Folder 4365A)
          - Fre-Fu, 1978-1979, 1981-1983, 1985-1994 (Box 199, Folder 4366)
          - Fre-Fu, 1978-1979, 1981-1983, 1985-1994 (Box 199, Folder 4366A)
        - G, 1968-1969, 1971-1972, 1974-1994
          - Ga, 1982-1984, 1986-1994 (Box 199, Folder 4367)
          - Ga, 1982-1984, 1986-1994 (Box 199, Folder 4367A)
          - Ge, 1982, 1984-1990, 1992, 1994 (Box 199, Folder 4368)
          - Ge, 1982, 1984-1990, 1992, 1994 (Box 199, Folder 4368A)
          - Gia-Gin, 1976-1978, 1980-1986, 1988-1992, 1994 (Box 200, Folder 4369)
          - Gia-Gin, 1976-1978, 1980-1986, 1988-1992, 1994 (Box 200, Folder 4369A)
          - Gillotte, Tony, 1978-1979, 1981-1982, 1985-1988, 1990-1991 (Box 200, Folder 4370)
          - Git-Gof, 1977-1978, 1981-1985, 1987-1989, 1992-1993 (Box 200, Folder 4371)
          - Git-Gof, 1977-1978, 1981-1985, 1987-1989, 1992-1993 (Box 200, Folder 4371A)
          - Gol-Gord, 1968-1969, 1971-1972, 1977, 1980-1991, 1993 (Box 200, Folder 4372)
          - Gol-Gord, 1968-1969, 1971-1972, 1977, 1980-1991, 1993 (Box 200, Folder 4372A)
          - Gorl-Grah, 1974-1975, 1981-1988, 1990-1993 (Box 200, Folder 4373)
          - Gorl-Grah, 1974-1975, 1981-1988, 1990-1993 (Box 200, Folder 4373A)
          - Gran-Gross, Marty, 1978-1991 (Box 201, Folder 4374)
          - Gran-Gross, Marty, 1978-1991 (Box 201, Folder 4374A)
          - Greenwald, Caroline, 1978-1985 (Box 201, Folder 4375)
          - Gross, Mimi-Gut, 1980, 1984-1994 (Box 201, Folder 4376)
          - Gross, Mimi-Gut, 1980, 1984-1994 (Box 201, Folder 4376A)
          - Gutman, Judith, 1976-1982 (Box 201, Folder 4377)
        - H, 1963, 1968-1969, 1972-1994
          - Haa-Hal, 1973, 1977-1979, 1981-1983, 1985-1991, 1993 (Box 201, Folder 4378)
          - Haa-Hal, 1973, 1977-1979, 1981-1983, 1985-1991, 1993 (Box 201, Folder 4378A)
          - Ham-Harm, 1981-1993 (Box 201, Folder 4379)
          - Ham-Harm, 1981-1993 (Box 201, Folder 4379A)
          - Harp-Hav, 1963, 1972-1974, 1976, 1978, 1981-1987, 1989-1991 (Box 202, Folder 4380)
          - Harp-Hav, 1963, 1972-1974, 1976, 1978, 1981-1987, 1989-1991 (Box 202, Folder 4380A)
          - Harlin, Michael, 1973,1975-1976, 1979, 1983 (Box 202, Folder 4381)
          - Harpman, Louise & Katherine D. Winter, 1991-1992 (Box 202, Folder 4382)
          - Harpman, Louise & Katherine D. Winter, 1991-1992 (Box 202, Folder 4382A)
          - Haw-Hen, 1978-1984, 1986-1993 (Box 202, Folder 4383)
          - Haw-Hen, 1978-1984, 1986-1993 (Box 202, Folder 4383A)
          - Hayman, Rihcard, 1975-1977, 1979-1981, 1987, 1990 (Box 202, Folder 4384)
          - Heinrich, Richard, 1984, 1986 (Box 202, Folder 4385)
          - Her, 1978, 1980-1987, 1990-1994 (Box 202, Folder 4386)
          - Her, 1978, 1980-1987, 1990-1994 (Box 202, Folder 4386A)
          - Hes-Hir, 1981-1982, 1984-1987, 1989-1994 (Box 203, Folder 4387)
          - Hes-Hir, 1981-1982, 1984-1987, 1989-1994 (Box 203, Folder 4387A)
          - Hod-Hoi, 1976-1978, 1983, 1985, 1987-1993 (Box 203, Folder 4388)
          - Hod-Hoi, 1976-1978, 1983, 1985, 1987-1993 (Box 203, Folder 4388A)
          - Hol-Hop, 1978-1979, 1983-1984, 1986-1987, 1990-1994 (Box 203, Folder 4389)
          - Hol-Hop, 1978-1978, 1983-1984, 1986-1987, 1990-1994 (Box 203, Folder 4389A)
          - Hor-How, 1977-1983, 1985-1986, 1988-1990, 1992-1993 (Box 203, Folder 4390)
          - Hor-How, 1977-1983, 1985-1986, 1988-1990, 1992-1993 (Box 203, Folder 4390A)
          - Hotung, Ann, 1980-1984, 1986 (Box 204, Folder 4391)
          - Hs-Hud, 1980, 1982, 1984-1991 (Box 204, Folder 4392)
          - Huf-Hy, 1982-1986, 1988-1994 (Box 204, Folder 4393)
          - Huf-Hy, 1982-1986, 1988-1994 (Box 204, Folder 4393A)
          - Hughes, Robert, 1978-1980, 1983-1987 (Box 204, Folder 4394)
          - Huntington, John C., 1968-1969, 1975-1976, 1986 (Box 204, Folder 4395)
        - I, 1963-1964, 1979-1980, 1982-1994 (Box 204, Folder 4396)
        - I, 1963-1964, 1979-1980, 1982-1994 (Box 204, Folder 4396A)
        - J, 1971-1972, 1975-1994
          - Jac-Jam, 1977, 1981, 1983, 1986-1994 (Box 205, Folder 4397)
          - Jac-Jam, 1977, 1981, 1983, 1986-1994 (Box 205, Folder 4397A)
          - Jan-Je, 1978, 1980, 1982-1987, 1990-1994 (Box 205, Folder 4398)
          - Jan-Je, 1978, 1980, 1982-1987, 1990-1994 (Box 205, Folder 4398A)
          - Joe-Jon, 1971, 1977-1980, 1982-1984, 1986-1989, 1991-1994 (Box 205, Folder 4399)
          - Joe-Jon, 1971, 1977-1980, 1982-1984, 1986-1989, 1991-1994 (Box 205, Folder 4399A)
          - Jor-Ju, 1972, 1975-1976, 1978, 1980-1984, 1987-1989, 1991-1994 (Box 205, Folder 4400)
          - Jor-Ju, 1972, 1975-1976, 1978, 1980-1984, 1987-1989, 1991-1994 (Box 205, Folder 4400A)
        - K, 1971-1994
          - Kab-Kan, 1982-1994 (Box 205, Folder 4401)
          - Kab-Kan, 1982-1994 (Box 205, Folder 4401A)
          - Kao-Kay, 1979; 1981-1986; 1989-1990. 1992-1994 (Box 205, Folder 4402)
          - Kao-Kay, 1979, 1981-1986, 1989-1990, 1992-1994 (Box 205, Folder 4402A)
          - Kea-Kennard, John, 1975, 1977, 1979-1981, 1983-1993 (Box 206, Folder 4403)
          - Kea-Kennard, John, 1975, 1977, 1979-1981, 1983-1993 (Box 206, Folder 4403A)
          - Kennedy, Leonard J.-Key, 1976, 1978-1979, 1981, 1983-1994 (Box 206, Folder 4404)
          - Kennedy, Leonard J.-Key, 1976, 1978-1979, 1981, 1983-1994 (Box 206, Folder 4404A)
          - Kie-Kim, 1974, 1980-1994 (Box 206, Folder 4405)
          - Kie-Kim, 1974, 1980-1994 (Box 206, Folder 4405A)
          - Kin-Kl, 1975, 1977, 1980, 1982-1994 (Box 206, Folder 4406)
          - Kin-Kl, 1975, 1977, 1980, 1982-1994 (Box 206, Folder 4406A)
          - Kn-Koh, 1977-1978, 1980-1994 (Box 207, Folder 4407)
          - Kn-Koh, 1977-1978, 1980-1994 (Box 207, Folder 4407A)
            Rerstricted from scholarly access-Confidential material
          - Kochi, William, 1986, 1991-1992 (Box 207, Folder 4408)
          - Kol-Kr, 1971, 1974-1976, 1980, 1982-1992, 1994 (Box 207, Folder 4409)
          - Kol-Kr, 1971, 1974-1976, 1980, 1982-1992, 1994 (Box 207, Folder 4409A)
          - Kotch, Nancy, 1985-1986 (Box 207, Folder 4410)
          - Ku-Ky, 1972-1973, 1979-1980, 1982, 1986, 1988-1989, 1991-1994 (Box 207, Folder 4411)
          - Ku-Ky, 1972-1973, 1979-1980, 1982, 1986, 1988-1989, 1991-1994 (Box 207, Folder 4411A)
        - L, 1964-1965, 1967-1974, 1976-1994, 1996
          - Laa-Lam, 1980, 1985-1992 (Box 207, Folder 4412)
          - Laa-Lam, 1980, 1985-1992 (Box 207, Folder 4412A)
            Restricted from scholarrly access-Confidential material
          - Lan-Lap, 1978-1980, 1986-1987, 1989-1994 (Box 208, Folder 4413)
          - Lan-Lap, 1978-1980, 1986-1987, 1989-1994 (Box 208, Folder 4413A)
          - Lat-Law, 1972, 1981-1988, 1990-1992, 1994 (Box 208, Folder 4414)
          - Lat-Law, 1972, 1981-1988, 1990-1992, 1994 (Box 208, Folder 4414A)
          - Lea-Lee, 1977, 1982, 1984-1988, 1990-1994, 1996 (Box 208, Folder 4415)
          - Lea-Lee, 1977, 1982, 1984-1988, 1990-1994, 1996 (Box 208, Folder 4415A)
          - Leg-Lem, 1987, 1989-1994 (Box 208, Folder 4416)
          - Leg-Lem, 1987, 1989-1994 (Box 208, Folder 4416A)
          - Len-Lev, 1971, 1981, 1984-1987, 1989-1994 (Box 208, Folder 4417)
          - Len-Lev, 1971, 1981, 1984-1987, 1989-1994 (Box 208, Folder 4417A)
          - Levines, Thomas, 1986-1990 (Box 209, Folder 4418)
          - Lew-Lig, 1970, 1983-1984, 1986-1994 (Box 209, Folder 4419)
          - Lew-Lig, 1970, 1983-1984, 1986-1994 (Box 209, Folder 4419A)
          - Lieberman, Marcia R., 1993-1994 (Box 209, Folder 4420)
          - Lieberman, Marcia R., 1993-1994 (Box 209, Folder 4420A)
          - Lim-Lob, 1973; 1976; 1978-1987; 1989-1993 (Box 209, Folder 4421)
          - Lim-Lob, 1973, 1976, 1978-1987, 1989-1993 (Box 209, Folder 4421A)
          - Linda, Mary, 1988 (Box 209, Folder 4422)
          - Linda, Mary, 1988 (Box 209, Folder 4422A)
          - Loc-Lor, 1976, 1978-1982, 1984-1987, 1992 (Box 209, Folder 4423)
          - Loc-Lor, 1976, 1978-1982, 1984-1987, 1992 (Box 209, Folder 4423A)
          - Loeffler, Carl, 1984-1988 (Box 210, Folder 4424)
          - Lomax, Alan, 1969-1974, 1981, 1986 (Box 210, Folder 4425)
          - Lord, Bette Bao, 1985-1991 (Box 210, Folder 4426)
          - Lord, Bette Bao, 1985-1991 (Box 210, Folder 4426A)
          - Lot-Lu, 1979-1988, 1990-1994 (Box 210, Folder 4427)
          - Lot-Lu, 1979-1988, 1990-1994 (Box 210, Folder 4427A)
            Rrestricted from scholarly access-Confidential material
          - Ly, 1964-1965, 1967-1968, 1980-1982, 1987, 1989, 1991-1993 (Box 210, Folder 4428)
          - Ly, 1964-1965, 1967-1968, 1980-1982, 1987, 1989, 1991-1993 (Box 210, Folder 4428A)
        - M, 1967, 1969-1970, 1974-1976, 1978-1994
          - Ma-Mah, 1967, 1974-1976, 1978-1982, 1985-1987, 1989-1994 (Box 210, Folder 4429)
          - Mai-Man, 1970, 1978-1982, 1984, 1986-1987, 1989-1993 (Box 210, Folder 4430)
          - Mai-Man, 1970, 1978-1982, 1984, 1986-1987, 1989-1993 (Box 210, Folder 4430A)
          - Mar, 1982-1994 (Box 211, Folder 4431)
          - Mar, 1982-1994 (Box 211, Folder 4431A)
          - Marashinsky, Amy Sophia, 1979-1983 (Box 211, Folder 4432)
          - Mas-McC, 1975, 1981-1985, 1987-1994 (Box 211, Folder 4433)
          - Mas-McC, 1975, 1981-1985, 1987-1994 (Box 211, Folder 4433A)
          - Matusky-Yamaguchi, Patricia, 1982, 1986, 1988-1990 (Box 211, Folder 4434)